他想让我们继承他的遗志
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
saving people, hunting things, the family business.
小子 今天是你的幸运日
Today's your lucky day, kid.
- 你能帮我看着萨姆吧？- 老爸 我会的 你知道我会的
- You watch out for Sammy, okay? - Dad, you know I will.
爸爸
Dad?
死亡时间 上午10：41
Time of death, 10:41 a.m.
我想父亲 我现在感觉很差
I miss him, man. And I'm not all right.
- 你感觉也不会好 - 我已经接受父亲已死这个事实
- Neither are you. - I'm dealing with Dad's death.
父亲已经死了 你却太伤心接受不了
Dad's dead. It hurts so bad you can't take it.
我很好 我发誓 下一次再有人问我这事
I'm okay. The next person who asks me if I'm okay…
我就给他几拳
I'm gonna start throwing punches.
好了 现在我们有啤酒…
Okay, we've got booze.
巧克力… 等一下 还有这个
We've got chocolate. And…Wait for it.
Emo乐队的摇滚音乐 保证可以除去任何伤痛
tortured emo rock, a guaranteed cure for any broken heart.
你不需要为我那么做
You didn't have to do all this.
- 我没事 - 是的 看得出来
- I'm fine. - Yeah, I can see that.
谢谢了 Neal
Thanks, Neil.
你真是够朋友
You're a good friend.
可能是他来了
Oh, God, it's probably him.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
- 她在哪？- 冷静一下 再想想发生了什么如何？
- Where is she? - Chill out. Think about this for a second.
- 我要和她谈谈 - 再找个时间谈吧
- I need to talk to her. - Some other time.
你给我走开
You get out of my face, Neil.
安吉拉
Angela?
让我… 一个人… 待着
Leave me alone.
安吉拉 抱歉
Angela, I'm sorry.
你说抱歉？
You're sorry?
- 你说抱歉？喔 真是太好了 - 安吉拉 听我说
- You're sorry. Oh, that's great. - Angela, listen to me.
我不想听你说 我已经听够了
I don't wanna listen to you. I'm done listening.
- 听我说 - 你怎么能这样对我？
- Listen to me. - No…
我曾那么爱你
I loved you.
安吉拉
Angela?
[邪恶力量 第2季第4集]
算了吧 萨姆 算我求你了 这样做很蠢
Come on, Sam, I'm begging you. This is stupid.
- 为什么？- 去妈妈坟前拜忌？
- Why? - Going to visit Mom's grave?
她连坟墓都没有 在那场火烧了之后连遗体也没有
She doesn't have a grave. There was no body left after the fire.
- 她有个石碑 - 是由我们素昧蒙面的叔叔立的碑
- She has a headstone. - Yeah, put up by a man we've never met.
你想对着一个由陌生人立的碑 来抒发你对母亲的爱
So you wanna go pay your respects to a slab of granite put up by a stranger?
- 这不是重点 - 那我要请教一下了
- That's not the point. - Well, then, enlighten me.
这不是关于遗体或棺材什么的
It's not about a body or a casket.
这是我们和她一起拥有的记忆 知道吗？
It's about her memory, okay?
父亲死后 就… 就感觉这是我们应该做的事
And after Dad, it just feels like the right thing to do.
- 这只是你的一厢情愿 - 听着 兄弟 没有人叫你一起去
- It's irrational, is what it is. - Look, man, no one asked you to come.
我们还不如去路边的酒吧抓鬼呢？
Why don't we swing by the Roadhouse?
最近我们都没有那恶魔的消息了
We haven't heard anything on the demon.
我们应该把那个贱魔给做了
We should be hunting that son of a bitch.
这主意不错 你去吧 让我在这下车 我再搭车回去
That's a good idea. You should. Just drop me off. I'll hitch a ride…
- 明天我们在那儿见 - 很好
- and I'll meet you there tomorrow. - Right.
和那些人鬼混
I'd be stuck with those people
谈些尴尬的事直到你出现
making awkward small talk until you show up.
不用了谢谢
No, thanks.
我想 嗯…
I think, um…
我想父亲想把这个给你
I think Dad would have wanted you to have these.
我爱你妈妈
I love you, Mom.
- 就是这样 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
安吉拉·梅森
Angela Mason.
她是当地的大学生 三天前刚下葬
She was a student at the local college. Funeral was three days ago.
接着呢？
And?
你看到她的坟墓了 坟周围一个圈内的所有生物都死了
You saw her grave. Everything dead around it in a perfect circle.
你不觉得这有点鬼异吗？
You don't think that's a little weird?
可能是土地主人洒了一点
Maybe the groundskeeper went aggro…
- 杀虫剂在上面 - 没有 我问过他了
- with the pesticide. - No, I asked him.
没有杀虫剂 化学物质 没人能对此做出解释
No pesticide, no chemicals. Nobody can explain it.
那好 你有什么想法？
Okay. So, what are you thinking?
我不知道 可能是污秽之地
I don't know. Unholy ground, maybe.
什么？
What?
如果真是恶魔 想那么干是轻而易举的事
If something evil happened, it could easily poison the ground.
还记得希达皮兹市旁农场发生的事吗？
Remember the farm outside of Cedar Rapids?
- 我知道 - 这个标记可能意味着恶魔的存在…
- Yeah. - Could be the sign of a demonic presence.
或是安吉拉这个女孩的灵魂
Or the Angela girl's spirit
如果她真有这个能耐的话
if it's powerful enough.
但也别那么激动 也许事情并不是你想的那样
Don't get too excited, you might pull something.
只是想着抓鬼…
It's just, stumbling onto a hunt?
- 到哪里都是这样？- 那怎么样？
- Here, of all places? - So?
那你是真的只想着抓鬼 不是心里还有别的事？
Are you sure this is about a hunt? Not about something else?
还会有什么事？
What else would it be about?
- 你知道 只想忘记它 - 你要相信你想要什么 萨姆
- You know, just forget it. - You can believe what you want, Sam.
但是你把我拖到这里来的 至少也要把这事查一下吧
But I let you drag my ass out here. Least we can do is check this out.
那好吧
Yep. Fine.
这女孩的父亲在镇里工作 他是学校里的教授
Girl's dad works in town. He's a professor at the school.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
- 梅森博士？- 我是
- Dr. Mason? - Yes.
我是萨姆 这是迪恩
I'm Sam. This is Dean.
我们是安吉拉的朋友
We were friends of Angela's. We…
我们… 我们想来慰问一下
We wanted to offer our condolences.
请进吧
Please, come in.
- 她真漂亮 - 是的 她很漂亮
- She was beautiful. - Yes, she was.
这书可不一般
This is an unusual book.
这是古希腊书籍 我教这门课
Oh, it's Ancient Greek. I teach a course.
那场车祸 这… 真是不幸
So a car accident, that's… That's horrible.
发生车祸时安吉离家只有一英里远
Angie was only a mile away from home when, uh…
像这样失去亲人
It's gotta be hard…
不是件容易的事
losing someone like that.
有时候你会感觉她还在你的身边
Sometimes it's like they're still around…
就像你还能感觉到她们的存在
almost like you can still sense their presence.
- 你有这样的感觉吗？- 事实上我有这样的感觉
- You ever feel anything like that? - I do, as a matter of fact.
梅森博士 有这种感觉很正常
That's perfectly normal, Dr. Mason.
特别是你在经历这样的事之后
Especially with what you're going through.
你知道吗 我还会给她打电话
You know, I still phone her.
直到电话响起我才想到她已死了 嗯…
And the phone's ringing before I remember that, uh…
家庭意味着一切
Family's everything, you know?
安吉是我生命中最重要的人
Angie was the most important thing in my life.
现在我失去了她
And now, well, I'm just lost without her.
真的很抱歉
We're very sorry.
肯定有什么不对劲 只是我们还没有察觉
There's something going on. We just haven't found it yet.
迪恩 有可能只是一块没长草的地 没什么特别的
Dean, so far you got a patch of dead grass and nothing.
肯定是有东西 让那块地变成污秽之地的
Something turned that grave into unholy ground.
没有理由可以证明 那就是块污秽之地
There's no reason for it to be unholy ground.
安吉拉是车祸死的 而且她是个好女孩
Angela Mason was a nice girl who died in a car crash.
那里并没有怨气存在 你听到她父亲
That's not exactly vengeful-spirit material. You heard her father.
你也听她父亲说了 也许她父亲并不知道她女儿的一切
Maybe Daddy doesn't know everything there is to know about his little angel.
你知道吗？我们不应该再打扰 那个可怜的父亲
You know what? We never should've bothered that poor man.
- 我们都不应该在这儿 - 那你是什么意思 萨姆？
- We shouldn't even be here anymore. - So, what, Sam? We just bail?
在我们还没把事情弄清楚之前就走人？
Without even figuring out what's going on?
我知道接下来该做什么
I think I know what's going on here.
这也是我陪你到现在的原因
It's the only reason I went along with you this far.
- 你在说什么啊？- 妈妈的坟墓
- What are you talking about? - This is about Mom's grave.
不知道你在说什么
It's got nothing to do with it.
你一直在她坟墓的百码之外 没靠近过
You wouldn't step within 100 yards of it.
听着 你也许在捕捉 那些想像中并不存在的东西
Look, maybe you're imagining a hunt where there isn't one…
这样你就可以不一直想着爸妈了
so you don't have to think about Mom or Dad.
如果你还出去走走？
You wanna take another swing?
那就去吧 如果这样做 真的会让你感觉好一点的话
Go ahead, if it'll make you feel better.
我不要听这些废话
I don't need this crap.
- 迪恩 你要去哪里？- 我要去喝一杯… 一个人
- Dean, where are you going? - I'm gonna go get a drink. Alone.
说真的 把照相机从我的脸上拿开
Seriously, get that camera out of my face.
什么 你害羞 我 事实上
What, you shy? I am, as a matter of fact.
也许这会帮助你克服它
Then maybe this'll help you overcome it.
我恨你
I hate you.
哦 骗子 你疯狂的爱着我 你知道的
Oh, liar. You're crazy about me and you know it.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我只是有一个想法 我们可以做一个完全不同类型的视频
You know, I just had an idea. We can make a whole different kind of video.
你这个混蛋
You jerk.
- 是的 但我是你的傻瓜 - 请关闭相机
- Yeah, but I'm your jerk. - Please turn the camera off.
你很美 你知道吗 你知道的 对吧
You're beautiful, you know that? You know that, right?
- 你是谁？- 等等 等等
- Who the hell are you? - Wait, wait, wait.
- 等一下 - 我要报警
- Hold on. - I'm calling 911!
- 我是安吉拉的堂兄 - 什么？
- I'm Angela's cousin. - What?
是的 她父亲让我来拿走她的东西
Yeah, her dad sent me over to, uh, pick up her stuff.
我名字是艾伦 艾伦·斯坦威克
Alan Stanwick My name's Allan. Allan Stanwick.
她父亲没说有人要来
Her dad didn't say that you were coming.
我的意思是…
Well, I mean…
那我怎么会有你这里的钥匙？
how else would I have the key to your place?
你一定看到了安吉拉的另一面
So I'm sure you got a view of Angela that none of the family got to see.
告诉我 她人怎么样？
Tell me, what was she like?
她这个人怎么样？她很好…
- What was she really like? - She was great.
很… 好
Just great.
我意思是她很…
I mean, she was so…
- 很好 - 是的
- Great. - Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
你们两个关系很好吧？
You two must've been really close, huh?
以前很好
We were.
但不是只是她 还有马特
But it's not just her. It's Matt.
- 谁？- 安吉拉的男朋友呀
- Who? - Angela's boyfriend.
是的 马特
Right, Matt.
- 嗯 他怎么了？- 他昨晚自杀了
- Um, what about him? - He killed himself last night.
他自己嗐喉自杀的 这是谁做的？
He cut his own throat. Who does that?
太… 不幸了
That's terrible.
他肯定不能承受安吉拉的死 我猜…
He was taking Angela's death pretty hard, and I guess…
- 我的意思是他这两天有点混乱 - 混乱什么？
- He'd been messed up about it for days. - Messed up how?
他一直说他到哪儿都能看见她
He kept saying that he saw her everywhere.
我想这是很正常的
Well, I'm sure that that's normal.
我意思是有这样的经历 说这样的话是正常的
I mean, with everything that he was going through.
他说他看见她…
He said that he saw her.
就像游魂一样
As in an acid trip or something.
安吉拉和马特是不是幸福的一对？
Were Angela and Matt a happy couple?
我是说马特有做什么事 让安吉拉生气吗？
Was there any reason Angela would be angry with him?
什么？
What?
不 当然没有 你为什么这样问？
No, of course not. Why do you ask?
随便问问
Just asking.
马特住在哪里？
Where did Matt live?
下一部要播出的电影是
Next on the Skin Channel:
《色情房屋4》讲述了两个拉丁美女…
Casa Erotica 4: A Tale of Two Latin Beauties.
嘿
Hey.
什么？
What?
尴尬
Awkward.
- 你到底去哪了？- 在跟我想像中的案子
- Where the hell were you? - Just working my imaginary case.
是吗？然后呢？
Yeah, and…?
喔 你是对的 我没什么新发现
Oh, well, you were right. I didn't find much.
是的 除了安吉拉男朋友昨晚死了… 切了自己的喉咙
Yeah. Except Angela's boyfriend died last night, slit his own throat.
但你知道这也很正常的 嗯 让我想想 还有什么？
But, you know, that's normal. Uh, let's see. What else?
在他死前 他说他在哪儿都能看见安吉拉
Oh, he was seeing Angela everywhere before he died.
你知道 这只是我自己瞎想而已
But, you know, I'm sure that's just me transferring my own feelings.
好了 我知道了 对不起了 那里也许真有脏东西
Okay, I get it. I'm sorry. Maybe there is something going on here.
只是也许？萨姆 不管你怎么想 我都知道该怎么做
Maybe? Sam, I know how to do my job, despite what you might think.
我们要查一下那个人的公寓
We should check out the guy's apartment.
我刚从那儿回来…
I just came from there.
那儿有一束死花 就和我们在墓地看到的一样
A pile of dead plants, just like the cemetery.
还有死金鱼
Hell, dead goldfish too.
- 真的是污秽之地？- 也许
- So unholy ground? - Maybe.
我始终不明白 那种怨恨之气会出自于安吉拉的
I'm still not getting that powerful angry- spirit vibe from Angela.
我正在看这个
I have been reading this, though.
你偷了那女孩的日记？
You stole the girl's diary?
- 是的 萨姆
Yeah, Sam.
- 这女孩有点太好了 - 那你接下来想做什么？
- If anything, the girl's a little too nice. - So, what do you wanna do?
- 继续调查 再和她的别的朋友谈谈 - 有他们的名字吗？
- Keep digging, talk to her friends. - You get any names?
你在开玩笑吧？
You kidding me?
我有她全世界朋友的的名字
I have her bestest friend in the whole wide world.
我不知道大学有雇悲痛辅导员
I didn't realize the college employed grief counselors.
是的 是的 你说我们听就可以了
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you talk, we listen.
也许再做一些心理治疗 来帮助你们心灵的痊愈
Maybe throw in a therapeutic collage. Whatever helps jump start the healing.
我想我没事 谢谢
Well, I think I'm okay. Thanks.
你知道马特·哈里森的事了吗？
Well, you heard what happened to Matt Harrison, right?
是的我知道了
Yeah, I did.
我只是想确认一下你没事
We just wanted to make sure you were okay.
悲伤有时会让人做出疯狂的举动
Grief can make people do crazy things.
听着 对于他的事我感到很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about what happened to him. I am.
但如果是马特自杀的话 那并不是因为悲伤而自杀
But if Matt killed himself, it wasn't because of grief.
- 不是吗？那是什么？- 是因为罪恶感
- No? Then why? - It was guilt.
- 安吉是死是马特的错 - 他自己也知道 为什么是他的错？
- Angie's death was Matt's fault. - How was Matt responsible?
她真的很爱他
She really loved that guy.
但那天晚上的车祸是因为 她看到他和另一个女孩在一起
But the night of the accident, she walked in on him with another girl.
她心都碎了 车祸就这样发生了
She was really torn up. That's why she crashed the car.
听着 我要去工作了
Um, look, I gotta get ready for work.
谢谢关心 不过说真的我真的没事
So thanks for the concern, but seriously, I'll be okay.
关于怨气的说法好像有点道理
Well, that vengeful- spirit theory is starting to make sense.
我意思是弃妇的怨气
I mean, hell hath no fury.
如果安吉拉已经对马特报了仇
So if Angela got her revenge on Matt
你认为一切是不是结束了？
you think it's over?
只有一个办法才能知道
Well, there's one way to be sure.
是吗？
Yeah?
- 什么办法？- 把尸骨烧了
- What's that? - Burn the bones.
烧尸骨？
Burn the bones?
你是不是有点晕
Are you high?
- 安吉拉上周才死 - 那又怎么样？
- Angela died last week. - So?
那她现在还没变成骨头
There's not gonna be bones.
棺材里还是一具完好正在腐烂的尸体
There's gonna be a ripe, rotting body in the coffin.
你什么时候怕脏了？
Since when are you afraid to get dirty, huh?
女士优先
Ladies first.
帮我拿着
Hold that.
我想你
I missed you.
他们在4天前埋的尸体
They buried the body four days ago.
我搞不懂了
I don't get it.
你瞧
Look.
- 那是什么？- 我不敢肯定
What is that? I'm not sure.
但之前我见过这些符号
I've seen these kinds of symbols before.
迪恩 别激动 好吗？
Dean, take it easy. Okay?
你们是安吉拉的朋友
You're Angie's friends, right?
- 梅森博士… - 我们得谈谈
- Dr. Mason…We need to talk.
好的 进来吧
Well, then, come in.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是教古希腊语的 告诉我…
You teach Ancient Greek. Tell me…
这些是什么意思？
what are these?
我不明白
I don't understand.
这和安吉拉有关吗
You said this had something to do with Angela.
是的 拜托 回答我的问题
It does. Please, just humor me.
他们是古希腊占卜仪式的一部分
They're part of an Ancient Greek divination ritual.
- 是做来施巫术的 对吧？- 是的
- Used for necromancy, right? - That's right.
你瞧 在来这之前 我们去过图书馆 自己做过一些调查
Before we came here, we stopped by the library and did a little homework.
事实上 他们是用这个来与死者沟通的
Apparently, they use rituals like this one for communicating with the dead.
甚至可以让尸体复活 根本就是还魂术
Even bringing corpses back to life, full- on zombie action.
是的
Yeah.
我是说 在传说中是的
I mean, according to the legends.
- 但这又有什么关系？- 你自己清楚
- Now, what's all this about? - I think you know.
- 迪恩 - 我明白
- Dean. - Look, I get it.
我也会想方设法地想再见某些人一面
Okay? There are people that I would give anything to see.
- 但是你有什么特权？- 迪恩
- But what gives you the right? - Dean.
- 你在说什么？- 该死的就不应该活着
- What? - What's dead should stay dead.
- 什么 - 你召回来的
- What? - What you brought back…
不是你女儿 那些东西是邪恶的 残暴的
isn't even your daughter. These things are vicious. They're violent.
它们肮脏之极 可以让周围的一切东西都腐烂
They're so nasty, they rot the ground.
得了吧 难道你没看过《宠物坟场》吗？
I mean, come on, haven't you seen Pet Sematary?
你疯了
You're insane.
- 她在哪？- 滚出我的房子
- Where is she? - Get out of my house.
我知道你把她藏起来了 她在哪？
I know you're hiding her somewhere. Where is she?
迪恩 住嘴吧 够了 迪恩 快看看
Dean, stop. That's enough. Dean, look.
这里的植物还是鲜活的
Beautiful, living plants.
- 我们走了 - 我要报警了
- We're leaving. - I'm calling the police.
我们很抱歉 先生 我们不会再来烦你了
Sir, we're sorry. We won't bother you again.
- 你到底是怎么了？- 离我远点
- What is the matter with you? - Back off.
那个人是无辜的 你不该那样对他
That man is innocent. He didn't deserve that.
看来她不在这里 也许他藏在别的地方了
Maybe he's keeping her somewhere else.
别说了 够了 好吗？够了
Stop it. That's enough, okay? Enough.
- 萨姆 我知道自己在干什么 - 不 你不知道… 一点都不
- Sam, I know what I'm doing. - No, you don't. At all.
我没那么容易被吓 但你这样吓坏我了
Dean, I don't scare easy, but you're scaring the crap out of me.
- 别想的那么戏剧化 - 萨姆 你很庆幸我们有事做了
- Don't be dramatic san. - You're lucky this turned out to be a case.
即使这不是 你也会找其它东西来猎杀
Because if it wasn't, you would've found something else to kill.
你的情绪现在很激动 很不稳定
You're on edge. You're erratic. Except for when you're hunting…
只有在抓鬼的时候 你才能真正宣泄你的情绪
because then you're downright scary.
你正在失去控制 伙计
You're tailspinning, man.
而且你避而不谈 也不让我来帮你
And you refuse to talk about it, and you won't let me help you.
- 我能照顾自己 谢谢了 - 不 你不能
- I can take care of myself, thanks. - No, you can't.
不 你不行 是你自己在给自己背上这个重担
You know what? You're the only one who thinks you should have to.
你不必独自挡起这事 没人可以
You don't have to handle this on your own. No one can.
如果你再敢提起老爸的死…
If you bring up Dad's death one more time
停 迪恩 它在折磨你
Stop. Please. Dean, it's killing you. Please.
我们已经失去老爸了
We've already lost Dad.
失去了妈妈
We've lost Mom.
我也失去了杰西卡
I've lost Jessica.
难道现在我要失去你了吗？
And now I'm gonna lose you too?
我们最好在警察到之前 离开这里
We better get out of here before the cops come.
我听到了 我很混球 对不起
I hear you. Okay? Yeah, I'm being an ass. And I'm sorry.
但有个变态的活死人在附近转悠
But we got a zombie running around.
我们必须得找出杀死它的方法
We need to figure out how to kill it.
对吧？
Right?
伙计 我们的生活真够古怪的
Our lives are weird, man.
可不是
You're telling me.
走吧
Come on.
亲爱的 有事在困扰你吗？
Honey, is something bothering you?
是马特
It's about Matt.
- 我们不是已经讲好的吗？- 我知道 但是 呃…
- Haven't we talked about that? - I know, but-
我们是不是 在他身上浪费太多时间了？
Haven't we wasted enough time on him already?
过来坐下
Come sit down.
你总是说他配不上我
You always said that he didn't deserve me.
- 你说对了 - 安吉拉
- You were right. - Angela…
你不会是去见过马特 或…
you didn't get out and go see Matt, or…?
我一直呆在这里啊
I've been here the whole time.
你真的认为我会做出那种事吗？
Neal… Neil, you really think I could do something like that?
没有 我…
No.
我不知道 总会不由自主地那么想
I don't know. I can't help it.
- 只是你… 你看起来… - 不同了？
- You just You seem - Different?
你是对的 我是不同了
You're right. I am.
我已经明白了…
I've realized…
你才是那唯一爱我的人
you're the only one who ever really loved me.
你已经证明过了
You proved that.
是你复活了我
You brought me back.
现在我和你在一起了
I'm with you now.
这不是你一直想要的吗？
Isn't that what you always wanted?
难道就不能给她脑门一枪吗？
We can't just waste it with a headshot?
老兄 你想得也太简单了
Dude, you've been watching way too many Romero flicks.
你是说 没有可以杀死活死人的办法？
So there's no lore on how to smoke them?
不是 我是说方法太多了
No, Dean, I'm telling you there's too much.
这里有上百种关于活死人的传说
There's a hundred legends on the walking dead…
杀死它们的方法也有上百种
but they all have different methods for killing them.
有的说用火烧
Some say setting them on fire.
还有的说… 在哪呢？
One said… Where is it?
在这儿 把它们的心脏拿去喂野狗
Right here. feeding their hearts to wild dogs.
那是我最喜欢的
That's my personal favorite.
但是谁知道其中的真伪啊？
Who knows what's real and what's myth?
- 有共同点吗？- 没有 只是有些说道银器可能管用
- Is there anything they have in common? - No. A few said silver might work.
- 那就先用银器吧 - 但是现在怎样才能找到安吉拉？
- Silver's a start. - Yeah. But how are we gonna find Angela?
- 那就得先找出是谁让她复活的 - 有线索吗？
- We gotta figure out who brought her back. - Any ideas?
如果不是她爸爸的话 那就可能是那个叫尼尔的了
I think if it's not her dad, it might be that guy Neil.
- 尼尔 - 是的
- Neal? - Yep.
- 你怎么知道的？- 你有张良计 我有过墙梯
- How'd you come up with that? - Well, you got your journal, I got mine.
「尼尔是个可以依靠的肩膀
"Neil's a real shoulder to cry on.
他很了解我和马特之间的事「
He so understands what I'm going through with Matt."
这里还有很多
There's more in here where that came from.
到处写满了这种无私奉献的爱意
It's got unrequited Duckie love all over it.
但是那不代表就是他做的
But that doesn't mean he brought her back from the dead.
嗯 我有提过 他是梅森教授的助教吗？
Mm. Did I mention that he's Professor Mason's TA?
他可以拿到一样的书籍
Has access to all the same books?
有人吗？
Hello?
尼尔
Neil.
你的悲痛辅导员来了 我们是来安慰你的
It's your grief counselors. We've come to hug.
银弹？
Silver bullets?
是的 足以打得她像个零钱包了
Yeah, enough to make her rattle like a change purse.
除非这是他藏A片的地方
Unless this is where he keeps his porn.
- 我看这里像个活死人的猪圈 - 是的
- Sure looks like a zombie pen to me. - Yeah.
但是空的
An empty one.
你认为安吉拉是去找什么人了吗？
You think Angela's going after somebody?
不 我想她是出去租电影了
No, I think she went out to rent Beaches.
听着 聪明人 她也许去杀人了
Look, smart-ass, she might kill someone.
我们得找到她 迪恩
We gotta find her, Dean.
知道
Yeah.
好吧 她杀了马特 因为他欺骗了她 对吧？
All right, she clipped Matt because he was cheating, right?
- 是的 - 要偷情的话 你知道的
- Yeah. - Well, it takes two to, you know…
都要成对的
have hardcore sex.
我不知道 我只是觉得
I don't know, it just seemed that Angela's roommate…
对马特的死很伤心
was broken up over Matt's death.
我是指 打心底的那种伤心
I mean, like, really broken up.
谁啊？
Hello?
你好啊 琳赛 我回来了
Hi, Lindsey. I'm home.
你清楚自己做了什么
You know what you did.
对不起 真的对不起
I'm sorry. I am so sorry.
那还不够
You're not sorry enough!
天哪
Oh, God.
哦 我的上帝啊 哦 我的上帝啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
好了 好了
Hey, I got you. I got you.
该死的 那个死小妞跑得真快
Damn, that dead chick can run.
然后呢？
What now?
该去找尼尔聊聊了
I say we go have a little chat with Neil.
那么 那些银弹 有些作用吧？
So the silver bullets, they did something, right?
是的 有些作用 但还不够 你还查到什么了？
Yeah, something. But not enough. What else you got?
呃
Um…
除了银器 我们还要 「把活死人顶在它们的棺材里」
Okay, besides silver, we have nailing the undead back into their grave beds.
这个被提到好几次了
It's mentioned a few times
也许这就是钉吸血鬼的由来吧
It's probably where the vampire staking lore came from.
- 它们的棺材？你认真的吗？- 是啊
- Their grave beds? You serious? - Yeah.
那我们要怎样 才能把安吉拉引到公墓啊？
How the hell are we gonna get Angela back to the cemetery?
你们来这做什么？
What are you guys doing here?
我听说过有人为了放倒女孩 而不择手段
I've heard of some people doing some desperate things to get laid
但是你
but you…
你却放倒一具尸体
You take the cake.
你们是谁？
Okay, who are you guys?
你或许该去问问安吉拉这个问题
You might wanna ask Angela that question.
- 什么？- 我们知道你做了什么
- What? - We know what you did.
仪式…
The ritual.
所有的一切
Everything.
你们疯了
Crazy.
你的女朋友是个死人 说我们疯了？
Your girlfriend's past her expiration date and we're crazy?
当人们死时 他们就得是死的
When someone's gone, they should stay gone.
你不能把那事给弄混了
You don't mess with that kind of stuff.
安吉拉杀了马特
Angela killed Matt.
还想要杀死琳赛
She tried to kill Lindsey.
我不知道你们在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
嗨 别废话了 尼尔
Hey. No more crap, Neil.
你的手上已经沾满了血
His blood is on your hands.
我和他可以平息这事 但你告诉我们她在哪
Now, me and him can make this right, but you gotta tell us where she is.
告诉我们
Tell us!
在我家 她在我家
My house. She's at my house.
你肯定吗？
Are you sure about that?
听着 她在哪其实并不重要
Listen, it doesn't really matter where she is.
只有一个办法可以阻止她
There's only one way to stop her.
那就在她的墓地再做次仪式
We've gotta perform another ritual over her grave.
从而颠倒你所做的
To reverse the one that you did.
我们需要一些黑根 瘢痕叶和一些蜡烛
We're gonna need some black root, some scar weed, some candles.
非常复杂 但是那会让这一切结束
It's complicated, but it'll get the job done.
几小时后她又会死去
She'll be dead again in a couple hours.
我想你应该和我们一起
I think you should come with us.
我说真的 尼尔 马上就跟我们走
I'm serious, Neil. Leave with us, right now.
不
No.
听我说
Listen to me.
尽快离开这里
Get out of here as soon as you can.
但是最重要的是要冷静
But most of all, be cool.
不要惊慌
No sudden movements.
不要惹她生气
Don't make her mad.
我们走吧
Let's go.
- 你说过你不会出去的 - 对不起
- You said you'd stay in the house. - I'm sorry.
我只是想见见你
I just needed to see you.
尼尔 求你了
Neil, please.
你得帮帮我
You have to help me.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
和我一起去公墓
Come with me to the cemetery.
尼尔 他们想要杀了我 我们得去阻止他们
Neil, they're trying to kill me. We have to stop them.
你是说要杀了他们吗？
You mean kill them.
那是真的喽…
It's true.
- 马特和琳赛 - 他们先伤害我的
- Matt and Lindsey. - They hurt me.
如果你爱我 你就不能让别人再次伤害我
If you love me, you'll make sure nobody hurts me again.
带我去公墓 然后等一切都结束后
Take me to the cemetery, and then all this will be over.
我们就能一起开始新的生活
We can start new lives together.
好的
Okay.
愿上帝助我 但是好的
God help me, but okay.
我去拿车
I'll go get the car.
你就… 就等在这里
Just… Just wait here.
尼尔 你看起来很紧张
Neil, you look nervous.
没有 我很好
No, I'm fine.
难道你… 想要抛弃我吗？
Were you going to leave me?
- 不 当然不会 - 你会的 不是吗？
- No, of course not. I…You were, weren't you?
你怎么能？
How could you?
- 尼尔 我爱你啊 - 安吉拉
- Neil, I loved you. - Angela
你真认为这可行吗？
You really think this is gonna work?
不 不一定
No, not really.
但是这我唯一能想到的了
But it was the only thing I could come up with.
等等 这不是你所想的
Wait. It's not what you think.
我没有想过要复活 但我还是我
I didn't ask to be brought back. But it's still me.
我仍是个人 求你了
I'm still a person. Please.
求你不要
Wait, don't!
该死的就不应该活着
What's dead should stay dead.
- 安息吧 - 是的 这次一定要了 好吗？
- Rest in peace. - Yeah. For good this time, okay?
你知道吗 这整个引诱安吉拉来公墓的假仪式计划
You know, the whole fake- ritual thing, luring Angela into the cemetery…
真的很高明
pretty sharp.
谢谢
Thanks.
但你一定要把我当成诱饵了吗？
But did we have to use me as bait?
我觉得你更合她的胃口 她喜欢那种吊儿郎当的帅哥
I figured you were more her type. She had pretty crappy taste in guys.
我想她弄断了我的手
I think she broke my hand.
你就是太脆弱了 我们待会去料理你的手
You're just too fragile. We'll get it looked at later.
你想要多待一会吗？
You wanna stay for a while?
不用了
No.
迪恩 怎么了？
Dean, what is it?
- 对不起 - 你
- I'm sorry. - You?
为了什么？
For what?
为了最近我所做的
The way I've been acting.
还有老爸
And for Dad.
我的意思是 他也是你的老爸
I mean, he was your dad too.
- 他的死是我的错 - 你在说什么呢？
- And it's my fault that he's gone. - What are you talking about?
我知道你已经想到了 我也是
I know you've been thinking it. So have I.
那并不难想到
Doesn't take a genius to figure it out.
在医院的时候 我的伤一下子全好了
Back at the hospital, you know, full recovery.
真是个奇迹
It was a miracle.
但是5分钟后 老爸死了 柯尔特也不见了
And five minutes later, Dad's dead and the CoIt's gone.
不要告诉我这之间没有关系
You can't tell me there's not a connection there.
我不知道那个恶魔是怎么得逞的
I don't know how the demon was involved.
也不知道到底是发生了什么事…
I don't know how the whole thing went down, exactly.
但是老爸是因我而死的
But Dad's dead because of me.
- 这我很清楚 - 我们都不肯定
- And that much I do know. - We don't know that. Not for sure.
萨姆…
Sam…
你和老爸…
you and Dad…
你们是我一生中最重要的亲人
you're the most important people in my life.
但现在…
And now…
我后悔自己被救了回来 萨姆 那样是违反常规的
I never should've come back, Sam. It wasn't natural.
看看现在
And now look what's come of it.
我本该死了
I was dead.
我不应该活着的
And I should have stayed dead.
你想要知道我的感受吗
You wanted to know how I was feeling.
就是这样的
Well, that's it.
所以告诉我
So tell me…
你要怎么说才能纠正这一切？
what could you possibly say to make that all right?